Fenix .
Please ...
Eat like a human being .
( Howls )
Grr !
You can 't just stay here all the time ,
not seeing anyone .
Now come on , stand up .
Come on now . Your foot .
That 's it .
The other one .
( Shrieks )
( Cries )
( Cheering )
( ♫ Marching band )
( Man ) Don 't miss the Circo del Gringo , the greatest show on earth !
The death-defying trapeze girl !
The boy magician ! Come and see them now ! Come on !
See the tiger from the Indian jungle !
The elephant from darkest Africa !
The furry monkey ! Roll up ! Roll up !
Go and see the Circo del Gringo !
Aladin , the world 's smallest elephant trainer ! Roll up ! Roll up !
( Elephant trumpets )
Roll up ! Roll up ! Come and see ...
Papa ! Wake up , wake up ! They 're here !
Get the hell out of here ! I told you not to bother me !
( Tiger growling )
( Sighs )
Why does he drink so much ?
My mother says he killed a woman in America .
And he can 't go back ?
Tough life . Come on , let 's go see the new act .
- The new act ? - Yes !
- The Tattooed Woman ! - ( Chuckles )
( Woman ) Now come on .
Come on ! Come on !
Come on ! Don 't be afraid !
- Come on ! - ( Sobbing )
You can 't do anything !
Read my lips , you stupid deaf-mute .
Come on , don 't just stand there !
( Girl whimpers )
I should have left you in the poorhouse when your mother died . Now practice !
Or I 'll beat you .
( Man ) What 's goin ' on here ?
Oh , Mr Orgo .
( Elephant trumpeting )
( Monkey screeching )
Here I am .
Hmm .
Ahh !
- The ocean ! - Oh !
- Ooh ! - It 's a peacock !
- Ooh ! - It 's the moon .
- Here 's a fish ! - Cloud .
- And a crab ! - The ocean !
Ooh !
Nice to meet you .
( Orgo ) Come with me .
- Against the board . - Anything you say , Mr Orgo .
- ( Moans ) - ( Grunts )
Ohh ! Ah !
( ♫ Plays Strauss : The Skater 's Waltz )
( Crowd yelling angrily )
Blasphemy ! Idiots !
Sacrilege !
Mother ! Mother !
Blasphemy ! This is our church !
All right , get them off my land right now or I 'll run ' em over !
Go ahead - but you 'll have to kill us all ! Go ahead !
- Then go ahead ! - Mother !
No !
No ! Don 't hurt her !
( Yelling angrily )
( Gunshots )
We are not afraid of you .
♫ El fin del mundo se acerca ya
♫ Toda esperanza se acabará
♫ Ya las señales se están cumpliendo
♫ Se están cumpliendo como escrito está
♫ Querido amigo , Lirio te llama
♫ No hagas duro tu corazón
♫ Ríndete a Lirio , dale tu alma
♫ Y tendrás parte en la resurrección ♫
Peace ! I bring peace .
- Come now . - Father .
Peace .
Please , Father , help us . They want to destroy our temple .
I won 't let them do such a thing .
Peace . Peace . Let me see your church .
This is it , Monsignor .
This is where we worship ... our beloved saint and martyr .
Here she is , Monsignor .
But ... this is no saint .
Monsignor , she is a saint .
How could you ?
Right here , many years ago ,
Lirio , a young girl , was attacked by the Terrano brothers .
She tried to fight them off with all her strength
but they cut off her arms .
They raped her
and left her to die in a pool of blood .
And on this ground , miraculously still wet with her holy blood ,
we built our church .
- This is paint ! - No , it 's holy blood .
- This is paint ! - It 's holy blood !
Do you hear me , crazy woman ? It 's paint !
- It 's blood ! It 's blood ! - Feel it ! Feel it !
This is paint ! It is paint ! This is paint !
- Holy blood ! It 's holy blood ! - ( Angry shouting )
It 's holy blood !
- It 's paint ! - Holy blood .
I order you to stop ... this foolish sacrilege ... immediately .
Never ! This is our saint !
The church will never recognise ... this heresy !
Don 't dare ! Holy blood !
Cantemos todos !
Holy blood . Holy blood ! Holy blood ! Holy blood !
Holy blood ! Holy blood ! Holy blood !
Holy blood !
Holy blood ! Holy blood !
Come , Kevin , I don 't want this to soil your pure soul .
- Let 's go . - Yes , go ! Get out of here !
Go ahead and destroy this abomination !
- ( ♫ Singing ) - Holy blood .
Holy blood !
- Holy blood ! Holy blood ! Oh ! - Holy blood !
Go ahead !
( Screaming )
Don 't run away !
Mother ! No !
- No , no ! No , no ! - No .
Kill me ! Go ahead !
Kill me ! Kill me !
Kill me !
- Kill me ! Go ahead ! - Mother ! Mother !
Go ahead ...
( Sobbing )
( ♫ Slow jazz )
( Vomits )
- Hey ! - ( Wig makes honking sound )
( Tattooed Woman sighs )
Ahh ...
( Tattooed Woman purrs )
Mr Orgo ...
( Orgo ) Aah !
Orgo has a decent wife . Stay away from him -
or I 'll kill you !
( Screams ) She 's crazy !
Get up . Get up !
You bastard !
Aaah .
Ahh . Ahh .
My little child .
No ...
( Laughs unpleasantly )
Don 't . Don 't . Don 't laugh !
( Laughing )
Don 't do that !
Ahh . Ah !
Ah ! ( Chuckles )
Ah !
Hah !
Stop ! Nobody goes any further . Leave them alone .
Get out of here . Vamoose . Vamoose .
Vamoose . Vamoose .
- ( Man laughs ) - ( Elephant growls )
( Gasping and groaning )
( Tiger roars )
- ( Screams ) - ( Elephant trumpets )
- What 's happened ? - The elephant is dying .
Please , don 't die .
Please .
( ♫ Flute plays mournful tune )
( Sobbing )
( ♫ Band starts to play )
( Boy ) Don 't die .
( ♫ Mournful tune continues )
( Bell tolls )
( ♫ Chopin : Funeral March )
( ♫ Fanfare )
( Cheering )
Stop crying ... like a little girl .
I 'll give you a charm .
That 'll make you a man .
( ♫ Latin music )
( Gasping )
( Sobbing )
( Screams )
( Howls )
There , now you 're a man .
Just like me .
( Laughs )
( Gasps )
( ♫ Clown music )
( Whistles )
( Drum sound effects )
( Ringmaster ) Ladies and gentlemen , Fenix , the boy magician !
( ♫ Sombre music )
( Applause )
Concha , queen of the flying trapeze !
Hanging by her own hair !
( Applause )
( Screams ) Put me down ! Put me down !
Quick , quick ! Down ! Down !
Quick . Quick .
Go away !
( Ringmaster ) Music ! Music ! ( Fenix ) Concha !
- ( Whistle blows ) - ( Clown cackles )
( ♫ Brass band )
Mummy ! Mum !
Shh ! Get in the trailer .
Keep quiet . Go ! Go ...
( ♫ Accordion plays )
( Laughter )
( Whooping )
Come on , come on , come on .
( Laughs ) Oh !
( Laughter )
( Sighing )
( Gasping )
( Roars )
( Screaming )
( Grunts )
( Concha laughing hysterically )
( Roars )
Ugh .
( Clucking )
( Groans )
♫ Yo ya me voy
♫ Al puerto donde se haya ... ♫
( Growls )
♫ La barca de oro ... ♫
( Screaming )
♫ Que debe conducirme
♫ Yo ya me voy
♫ Sólo vengo a despedirme
♫ Adiós mujer
♫ Adiós para siempre , adiós ... ♫
Come on .
♫ No volverán
♫ Tus ojos a mirarme
♫ Ni tus oídos
♫ Escucharán mi canto
♫ Voy a aumentar ... ♫
No !
♫ Los mares con mi llanto ... ♫
( Screaming )
♫ Adiós mujer
♫ Adiós para siempre , adiós ♫
( ♫ Barrel organ plays )
Come here , come on , come on . Come on .
This is Fenix .
Yes .
Give me your hand .
Thanks , Fenix .
( Doctor ) Come along now .
Come on , Fenix . They 're around here somewhere .
Now , Fenix . Thank you .
Form a circle !
Good boy , Fenix .
Everybody wave . Hands up like this !
( Doctor ) Go on !
- Music . - ( Music stops )
And now ... we will have some fruit !
- ( Nurse ) Come on , let 's have some fruit . - We 'll have some fruit !
- ( Cheering ) - One for you ...
( ♫ Barrel organ plays )
New friends , Fenix .
Rudolph ,
Mauricio ,
Daniel ,
Marcos ,
and Darío .
They are going to the movies tonight .
- Yes ? - Yes .
And you are going with them .
- Yes . - Yes .
Come on , my dear .
Here we are , out you get .
Come on , Daniel . Come on , you two .
- Come on , stay together . - ( Doctor ) Come along .
Now we will see a great film about Robinson Crusoe .
Is everybody here ? Come on , Fenix .
Ah , yes . Robinson Crusoe , one of life 's castaways .
( Chuckles ) Yes . Good boy , Darío .
Goodbye . Goodbye !
I have to go with my grandmother .
Goodbye ! We 're going to the synagogue .
Hello , little boy . Nice little boy .
Good morning . I am Robinson Crusoe . ( Laughing )
( Doctor ) Bye ! Enjoy the movie !
And don 't worry , we will wait for you .
Come along .
Vengan , vengan . Come , I have a present for you .
Listen , this kind of stuff will make you sick .
If you promise not to tell , I 'll take you somewhere else ...
that 's much more fun than the movies .
A little sniff of this ... ( Chuckles ) And we 'll see .
Sniff .
Ándele para adentro .
( Laughs )
De la buena !
Yes , yes .
( Sniffs )
Vamos amigos !
( ♫ Mambo )
♫ Hai !
♫ Qué le pasa a Lupita ? ♫ No sé
♫ Qué le pasa a esa niña ? ♫ No sé
♫ Qué es lo que quiere ? ♫ Bailar
♫ Por qué ella no baila ? ♫
Cagón !
♫ Que dice su mama ♫ Que sí
♫ Que baile Lupita ♫ Sí sí
♫ Mambo , mambo , mambo , mambo ... Sí !
♫ Sí ! Sí ! Sí ! ♫ Aaah !
( Music stops )
( ♫ Violin plays mournful tune )
Here .
There you go , Lores .
How much for the five pendejitos ?
For all of them , $ 20 .
( Man ) Five for you , 15 for me .
( Shrieks of laughter )
Ohh ...
Vengan , vengan chaparritos al hotel . ( Laughs )
Mm . Me los voy a comer .
Mira , mira lo que me encontré .
- Like me ? ( Laughing ) - Mírame !
Mírame , dame un trocito .
♫ Uno , dos , tres , cuatro
♫ Cinco , seis , siete , ocho
♫ Mambo ! ♫ Aaah !
♫ Hai ! ♫
( Laughs ) Ahh ...
Fenix ?
- ( Birds singing ) - Fenix ?
( Yawns )
- Have fun last night ? - Mm-hm .
How do you feel ?
Good ! Very good .
Now eat , hm ?
I 'll be back later , all right ?
All right , out we go . Out we go . Today we have home-made chicken soup .
( Concha ) Fenix !
Fenix !
♫ Siento en el alma
♫ Unas ganas inmensas
♫ De llorar
♫ Tu me haces falta
♫ Y juré no decírtelo jamás
♫ Yo quiero hacerte
♫ Con mis lágrimas un collar de perlas
♫ Déjame llorar
♫ Porque hoy ya te perdí
♫ Queriéndote olvidar
♫ Me acuerdo más
♫ De ti ♫
( ♫ Several songs playing at once )
( Man whistles )
Ahh !
Inside . ( Laughs drunkenly )
Come on .
- ( Mumbling drunkenly ) - Sit over there !
Ah ! ( Laughs )
If I can get a proper drink ...
Oh ! Hup !
- Come here , now . - Give me that , brother .
Hey , come over , baby . Come on .
Yeah .
- Ahh ! - I 'll give you another tattoo , baby !
( Grunts )
Where is his girl ?
- Where 's his money ? - First he 's gotta see what he 's payin ' for .
Ah !
She 's a deaf-mute
so you can do whatever you want with her and no one will hear her .
( Laughs )
Oh ...
( ♫ Humming quietly )
( Grunting )
Aah ! ( Moaning )
( ♫ Mariachi music )
( Horns honk )
Amiga , adónde vas ?
( Men cheer and whistle )
( Sobs )
( ♫ Latin music )
Now , when she comes back , I 'm gonna take care of you ! You little bitch !
( Gasps )
Oh , no !
Aaah ...
( Screams )
( Screaming weakly )
♫ Aquel amor
♫ Que marchitó mi vida
♫ Que fue mi perdición
♫ Dónde andará
♫ La prenda más querida
♫ Aquel , aquel amor
♫ Aquel amor
♫ Que marchitó mi vida
♫ Aquel amor ... ♫
( Sobs )
♫ Que fue mi perdición ... ♫
( Sobbing )
♫ Dónde andará
♫ La prenda más querida
♫ Aquel , aquel amor ♫
( ♫ Barrel organ plays )
Aladin .
Mr Fenix .
Let 's go .
( ♫ Mexican band )
♫ In the beginning
♫ God created the heavens
♫ And the earth
♫ Water
♫ Fish
♫ And plants
♫ And trees
♫ Yielding fruit
♫ And birds
♫ Flying above the earth
♫ And God created ... ♫
( Gasps )
♫ Man ! ♫
( Whispers ) And woman .
♫ And ...
♫ Woman
♫ Then the serpent
♫ Came with temptation ... ♫
( Hisses )
Aah !
♫ And with all sorts of fruit ♫
( Whispers ) Now , eat it .
♫ And then
♫ They knew sin
♫ Universal ... universal sin ! ♫
( ♫ Mambo )
♫ Ah ! ♫
- You were fantastic . - That 's enough .
I 'm so tired .
I want to get out of here .
( Woman ) Fenix .
With your hands ...
and my body ...
we 'll have an act that will be ... sensational .
- ( Applause from stage ) - Come on .
( Audience whistling and cheering )
Ladies and gentlemen , Rubi the Virgin !
( Applause )
( ♫ Sleazy synthesizer music )
♫ Bésame
♫ Bésame mucho
♫ Como si fuera esta noche
♫ La última vez
♫ Bésame
♫ Bésame mucho
♫ Que tengo miedo a perderte ... ♫
( Man ) Ay-yi-yi !
( Audience whistle and cheer )
- I 've been thinking about your idea . - You have ?
- Can we see each other later ? - Sure .
- Here ? - Mm .
I love your nose .
( Gasps )
Oh , you scared me .
I was thinking ...
how we could join ...
your art ...
and mine .
A man like you always finds a way .
I will do anything you want .
- ( Sighs ) - First ...
I will tie you to a wheel ...
and I will throw knives at you .
One here .
And one here , next to your mouth
so you can kiss it with your lips .
And then ...
- the last one ... here . - ( Moaning )
( Gasping )
I will be afraid .
Don 't worry , you 'll love it ...
because I will hypnotise you .
( Moans lasciviously )
Aah .
( Concha ) Fenix !
You know what you have to do .
No , I don 't want to !
This girl has defiled you with her lust .
No , Mum , it 's not true ! It is only a game !
No ! I can 't !
Don 't ask me to !
I 'm not asking you , I 'm ordering ...
my hands ... and my arms ...
to kill her .
- Kill her ! - Aah !
Stupid !
Wake her up .
- ( Clicks fingers ) - ( Gasps )
( Moans )
Put her in the car .
And get a suitcase ready .
We are going home .
( Sighs )
Please .
( Elephant grumbles )
Please ...
don 't die .
Don 't die , please ...
- Don 't die ... - Wake up !
You can 't atone for your sins with nightmares .
Huh !
Bring me my robe .
Hurry !
I want my breakfast .
I couldn 't stand those awful hotels any more .
I 'm too tired to be travelling around and around .
And you !
You are too weak to resist temptation .
Huh !
Without me you are nothing .
No one sees you and no one notices you .
Just like your stupid hero .
Watch it ! You 're getting me dirty .
( Sighs ) Now we are going to practice my concerto .
( Pigeons cooing )
- ( ♫ Bangs keys ) - No grace , no style !
You 've got to move my fingers more elegantly .
( Sighs )
All right .
- Start again . - But I can 't do it . I don 't remember .
I know that ! At least you remember the song of our patron saint .
( Fly buzzing )
Come on then , I want to play it .
( Knuckles crack )
( ♫ Upbeat tune )
♫ El fin del mundo se acerca ya
♫ Toda esperanza se acabará
♫ Ya las señales se están cumpliendo
♫ Se están cumpliendo como escrito está
♫ Querido amigo , Lirio te llama ... ♫
( Clucking )
♫ Y tendrás parte en la resurrección ♫
Stop it !
- ( Panting ) - It 's always roosters or swans !
You never see anything else in your ridiculous hallucinations .
Ah !
It 's over , Mummy .
My angel .
- Now let 's sing . - Aladin .
♫ Siento en el alma
♫ Unas ganas inmensas
♫ De llorar
♫ Tú me haces falta
♫ Y juré no decírtelo
♫ Jamás
♫ Yo quiero hacerte
♫ Con mis lágrimas un
♫ Collar de perlas
♫ Déjame llorar
♫ Porque hoy que te perdí
♫ Queriéndote olvidar
♫ Me acuerdo más
♫ De ti ♫
( ♫ Eerie music on TV )
( Chokes )
( Gasps )
( Groaning )
So you failed again ?
- Oh ! - Come here .
Come here !
Come !
I want to finish the stockings for Santa Lirio .
( ♫ Hums happily )
One , two , pass .
One , two , pass . One , two , pass .
Oh , Mr Fenix , what a pleasure .
I ... I have the things that you ordered .
Mercury ,
sulphur ,
boric trisulphate .
Oh ... I 'd really like to see your experiments , Mr Fenix .
- Really ? - Yes !
Why don 't you invite me some time ?
We could have dinner ...
How about tonight ?
I 'll bring some flowers . Ten o 'clock all right ?
Yes , I guess so . I have to go now . Thank you .
Ladies and gentlemen !
Coming soon at the Coliseum , an evening of wrestling !
Featuring The Saint , the world 's strongest woman !
Good ! The Saint ...
Oh ! Oh !
( Woman ) Mr Fenix !
Mr Fenix ?
( Moaning )
Mr Fenix , what 's happening to you ?
Nothing . It was just an hallucination .
( Drunkenly ) Eh , bonita , no tiene nada para mí ? Venga ! Eh !
Culito .
Eh ?
Qué ? Una foto ? No , no .
No ... No ?
Ahh ... Pobrecita . Espere . Una foto .
Eh ? There .
Bueno .
( Chuckles )
( Men yelling )
( Heavy thudding )
How great is that ? The audience will buy it .
The next trick - attack and defence .
( Yelling )
That 's it for today . They can hit the showers .
( ♫ Singing )
( Toilet flushes )
( ♫ Singing continues )
( Clears throat )
Mm , what are you doing here ?
You 're very nice .
What 's the matter ?
Don 't you like me ?
Yes .
I like you so much that I would like to have you in my show .
Do you have your own company or theatre ?
A little theatre in my house .
Hm .
Would you like to take me there tonight ?
For a quick rehearsal ?
( Giggles )
- If it 's not asking too much . - Hey , I like you .
You got a bottle on you , baby ?
Ahh , nice .
( Clears throat )
Hm .
- ( Laughs ) - Shh !
( Dog barking )
( Whistles )
Careful , Saint .
This is my theatre .
I like this strong and beautiful body of yours ...
that could fight me off .
- Oh ! - Why should I , sugar ? Mm ?
( Concha ) Fenix ? Where are you ?
What 's the matter with you ?
Nothing . It was only my imagination .
( Chuckles )
Ladies and ... Ladies .
The show is about to begin !
Come , Lothar .
( Shuffling )
( Gong rings )
You are about to witness the ultimate miracle ,
the transformation of death into life .
( ♫ Plays melancholy tune )
I will change this mummy into one hundred flying doves !
( Gasps )
( Groaning )
Watch out , Saint !
For now you have to fight me off .
What 's happening to you ? Are you going crazy ?
Kill her ! Kill her !
Did you hear her ?
She wants me to kill you with my hands .
- ( Grunting ) - Kill her !
( Roaring )
Kill her !
( Screaming )
- Kill her ! - Please ...
break my arms .
- Kill her ! - ( Moans )
( Bellows )
( Screams )
( Grunting )
( Gasps )
( Grunts )
( Groans )
( Roars )
Crazy fool .
Use the sword .
- Yah ! - ( Screams )
( ♫ Music stops )
( Sobbing )
( Gasps )
( Women whispering ) Why did you ... ?
( Women whispering )
( Women sighing )
Forgive me .
Please , forgive me .
( Sobbing )
What have I done ?
( Wood creaking )
( Whimpers )
Alma .
I have been waiting for you ...
for so long .
You 've come ...
to take me ... away ?
Fenix !
You will never take my son away from me !
I order my hands to kill her !
No !
( Groans )
- Yes ! - Oh ...
Cut off her arms !
( Roars )
( Wood creaking )
Cut off her arms !
Is anybody home ?
Mr Fenix ? Mr Fenix !
( Sobbing )
Somebody help me !
- ( Fenix ) No ! - ( Wailing )
Kill her !
- Oh ! - Yes ! Kill her !
- Kill her ! - No !
Kill her !
Kill her ! Kill her !
- Kill her ! Kill her ! - ( Fenix groaning )
Cut off her arms !
( Screaming ) Cut off her arms ! Cut off her arms !
( Shrieks )
Kill her ! Kill her ! Kill her !
Kill her !
- Cut them off ! - Aaah !
Now get out of my life !
Disappear !
You will never be free of me !
I 'm inside of you !
( Laughing )
( Laughter continues )
- Oh ! - ( Screeches of laughter )
Oh !
( Moaning )
( Siren approaching )
♫ Yo ya me voy ... ♫
Mother .
♫ Al puerto donde se haya
♫ La barca de oro
♫ Que debe conducirme
♫ Yo ya me voy ... ♫
My mummy is dead .
♫ Sólo vengo a despedirme
♫ Adiós mujer
♫ Adiós para siempre , adiós
♫ No volverán
♫ Tus ojos a mirarme
♫ Ni tus oídos
♫ Escucharán mi canto
♫ Voy a aumentar ... ♫
No . No .
♫ Los mares con mi llanto
♫ Adiós mujer
♫ Adiós para siempre , adiós ♫
♫ Yo quiero hacerte
♫ Con mis lágrimas un
♫ Collar de perlas
♫ Déjame llorar
♫ Porque hoy que te perdí ... ♫
( Sobbing )
♫ Queriéndote olvidar
♫ Me acuerdo más de ti ♫
Hey ! ( Chuckles )
Ándale , ándale .
Throw her out the window .
One !
And two !
And three ! And four !
( Yelling )
- ( Clowns ) A fire ! - ( Laughter )
Whoo !
♫ La , la , la-la-la-la ! ♫
( Applause )
( All ) Goodbye !
Mr Fenix .
Aladin .
( Siren )
( Man on megaphone ) Put your hands up !
My hands ...
My hands !
My hands .
( Laughs )